<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BOX Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://box.online.mills.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:13:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Latest Updates on Tyreek Hill Incident</title>
		<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/latest-updates-on-tyreek-hill-incident/</link>
					<comments>https://box.online.mills.edu/latest-updates-on-tyreek-hill-incident/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://box.online.mills.edu/?p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It has been almost a week now since the incident involving Miami Dolphins wide receiver Tyreek Hill at a North Miami Beach marina, and there remains a lot that is unknown. What we do know is that the investigation by Miami-Dade Police remained open as of Friday, according to UPI. Details of the incident remain</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/latest-updates-on-tyreek-hill-incident/">Latest Updates on Tyreek Hill Incident</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It has been almost a week now since the incident involving Miami Dolphins wide receiver Tyreek Hill at a North Miami Beach marina, and there remains a lot that is unknown.</p>



<p>What we do know is that the investigation by Miami-Dade Police remained open as of Friday, according to UPI.</p>



<p>Details of the incident remain as murky as ever, though, with&nbsp;<em>The Miami Herald&nbsp;</em>and South Florida ABC affiliate WPLG each reporting that tarpon fishing from the dock, which is not allowed, played a role in the dispute and the police report indicating that what led to Hill allegedly slapping a man in the back of the head was two women stepping onto a boat and being asked to leave.</p>



<p>Hill and his agent, Drew Rosenhaus, both posted videos of their fishing outing on Father&#8217;s Day that included Rosenhaus jumping into the ocean to touch a shark near the boat, but neither has commented on the incident.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="the-davante-adams-situation">THE DAVANTE ADAMS SITUATION</h3>



<p>A report in the <em>Kansas City </em>Star on Friday indicated that criminal charges were dropped against Raiders star wide receiver Davante Adams, charges stemming from an incident after a Monday night game at Arrowhead Stadium in October when Adams was seen on video shoving a man carrying photo/video equipment after he walked in front of him.</p>



<p>Adams still is facing a civil lawsuit from the victim, and Pro Football Talk suggested Saturday morning that Adams now could be facing disciplinary action from the NFL through its Code of Conduct policy.</p>



<p>This, of course, relates to Hill in a couple of ways, the first being how long it took for that particular assault case to be resolved, and the second being the potential of an NFL investigation.</p>



<p>WPLG reporter Ian Margol said an NFL representative was at the Haulover Marina on Friday.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="the-hill-incident-police-report">THE HILL INCIDENT POLICE REPORT</h3>



<p>The <em>South Florida Sun-Sentinel first </em>revealed the contents of the police report of the incident, which alleged that Hill hit a man in the neck and later charged at him before being restrained by members of his group.</p>



<p>On Wednesday, before the Sun-Sentinel report, South Florida radio host Andy Slater, citing sources, reported that police had closed the matter and the alleged victim would have to go to the state attorney&#8217;s office if he wished to press criminal charges.</p>



<p>According to the police report, the incident involving Hill began when two women got on a charter fishing boat without permission and were asked to leave. After an argument, the unidentified “subject” (believed to be Hill) slapped one of the employees on his neck with an open hand while he was being removed from the argument and ran toward the victim, but several people restrained him.</p>



<p>The subject then fled the area, according to the report.</p>



<p>The Dolphins issued a statement regarding the situation, and it pretty much was what one should expect in circumstances like these.</p>



<p>“We are aware of the situation and have been in contact with Tyreek, his representatives and the NFL,&#8221; the statement read. &#8220;We will reserve further comment at this time.”</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="what-happens-next">WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?</h3>



<p>With the Dolphins done with the offseason program and the start of training camp more than a month away, this is the time of year when no news is good news when it comes to players.</p>



<p>The Dolphins no doubt will continue to monitor the situation, as will the NFL and the league&#8217;s Code of Conduct could come into play depending on how things play out.</p>



<p>Hill is heading into his second season with Miami after a first one that met — if not exceeded — all expectations the team could have had when it sent five draft picks to the Kansas City Chiefs to consummate the trade.</p>



<p>Not only did Hill earn team MVP and All-Pro honors, he was a tone-setter with his practice habits and confident approach from the start of the offseason program.</p>



<p><strong>He&#8217;s looking for bigger and better things in 2023, saying after the final practice of minicamp his goal was to reach 2,000 receiving yards.</strong></p>



<p>The weekend incident, though, brought back earlier off-the-field incidents that threatened to derail his career — he was dismissed from Oklahoma State after being charged with domestic abuse (he later pleaded guilty) and was investigated in 2019 for alleged battery, though the case was dropped after medical reports indicated his 3-year-old son&#8217;s arm was broken bracing for a fall. The NFL investigated Hill but ultimately did not suspend him after concluding he had not violated the league&#8217;s code of conduct policy.</p>



<p>After the trade with the Chiefs, Dolphins GM Chris Grier was asked about the kind of background work that was done regarding Hill.</p>



<p>“Going forward, we feel good about it,&#8221; Grier said. &#8220;We talked to a number of people that have been around Tyreek, especially in Kansas City the last few years. For us, we’re comfortable moving forward and the expectation, like him, will be for every player on the roster — it’s to be a good teammate and a good citizen in South Florida.”</p>



<p>Hill has been doing football camps on a regular basis this offseason, including one in Boca Raton late this week.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/latest-updates-on-tyreek-hill-incident/">Latest Updates on Tyreek Hill Incident</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://box.online.mills.edu/latest-updates-on-tyreek-hill-incident/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Luka Modric: Net Worth, Salary, Achievements, Records, Car Collections, and More</title>
		<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/luka-modric-net-worth-salary-achievements-records-car-collections-and-more/</link>
					<comments>https://box.online.mills.edu/luka-modric-net-worth-salary-achievements-records-car-collections-and-more/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://box.online.mills.edu/?p=84</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Luka Modric is a Croatian professional football player who captains his national team and also plays for Real Madrid. He has played 166 games (24 goals) for Croatia till June 2023. Whereas for Real Madrid, since 2012, he has played 327 games (26 goals). Modric has been applauded by football pundits and his fellow players</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/luka-modric-net-worth-salary-achievements-records-car-collections-and-more/">Luka Modric: Net Worth, Salary, Achievements, Records, Car Collections, and More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Luka Modric is a Croatian professional football player who captains his national team and also plays for Real Madrid. He has played 166 games (24 goals) for Croatia till June 2023. Whereas for Real Madrid, since 2012, he has played 327 games (26 goals).</p>



<p>Modric has been applauded by football pundits and his fellow players for stunning long-range shots and his creative playmaking skills. Luka Modric before joining Real Madrid in 2012, played for various clubs like Dinamo Zagreb (2003-08), and Tottenham Hotspur (2008-12) as well.</p>



<p><strong>Age:&nbsp;</strong>37<br><strong>Date of Birth:</strong>&nbsp;9 Sep 1985<br><strong>Height:</strong>&nbsp;5 feet 8 inches (1.72 m)<br><strong>Position:</strong>&nbsp;Midfielder</p>



<p>Luka Modric&#8217;s&nbsp;<strong>net worth is estimated to be $75 million&nbsp;</strong>according to sources like celebritynetworth. He is r<strong>eported to earn $20 million per year&nbsp;</strong>from his contracts with football games and also from other endorsements and sponsors as well.</p>



<p>Luka Modric endorsements or sponsorship deals involve brands or companies like&nbsp;<strong>Nike, SofaScore (Sports company), and OlyBet (Online Betting platform).&nbsp;</strong>Modric owns a&nbsp;<strong>mansion in Madrid worth $13.07 million and he also owns a villa in Croatia worth $5.44 million.</strong>&nbsp;He also&nbsp;owns luxurious cars like B<strong>entley Continental GT ($2,25,000) and Audi Q7 ($65,000).&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p><strong>Records and Achievements:</strong><br>* Won three La Liga titles with Real Madrid in 2016-17, 2019-20, 2021-22<br>* FIFA WC runners-up with Croatia in 2018<br>*&nbsp; Won five UEFA Champions League titles with Real Madrid<br>* Won five FIFA Club World Club titles with Real Madrid in 2014, 2016, 2017, 2018, 2022<br>* Runners-up in UEFA Nations League for Croatia in 2022-23<br>* Won FIFA Club World Cup Silver Ball in 2016<br>* Won FIFA World Cup Golden Ball Award in 2018<br>* Won four UEFA Super Cup titles with Real Madrid in 2014, 2016, 2017 &amp; 2022<br>* Won Golden Foot Award in 2019<br>* Won Croatian Super Cup in 2006* Won &nbsp;Ballon d&#8217;Or in 2018</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/luka-modric-net-worth-salary-achievements-records-car-collections-and-more/">Luka Modric: Net Worth, Salary, Achievements, Records, Car Collections, and More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://box.online.mills.edu/luka-modric-net-worth-salary-achievements-records-car-collections-and-more/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senior Women Football C&#8217;ship: Haryana set up SF match with Odisha, Indian Railways to meet Tamil Nadu</title>
		<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/senior-women-football-cship-haryana-set-up-sf-match-with-odisha-indian-railways-to-meet-tamil-nadu/</link>
					<comments>https://box.online.mills.edu/senior-women-football-cship-haryana-set-up-sf-match-with-odisha-indian-railways-to-meet-tamil-nadu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://box.online.mills.edu/?p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the curtain came down on the Group Stage matches of the Senior National Women&#8217;s Football Championship, 2023, on Saturday, 24 June, a clear picture emerged on the semi-finals line-ups of the prestigious meet.In the penultimate rounds to be played on Monday, June 26, mighty Tamil Nadu, who swept Group A with five wins from</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/senior-women-football-cship-haryana-set-up-sf-match-with-odisha-indian-railways-to-meet-tamil-nadu/">Senior Women Football C&#8217;ship: Haryana set up SF match with Odisha, Indian Railways to meet Tamil Nadu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the curtain came down on the Group Stage matches of the Senior National Women&#8217;s Football Championship, 2023, on Saturday, 24 June, a clear picture emerged on the semi-finals line-ups of the prestigious meet.<br>In the penultimate rounds to be played on Monday, June 26, mighty Tamil Nadu, who swept Group A with five wins from five outings, will cross swords with Indian Railways in the day&#8217;s first match. Later in the day, Group B winners Haryana will take on Odisha, as per a press release from All India Football Federation (AIFF).<br>On Saturday, at the GNDU main ground, Haryana needed only a point to edge Indian Railways in the battle for the top spot in Group B and they did exactly that. A 2-2 draw against Bengal was enough to take them to 13 points, a point ahead of the Railways.</p>



<p>For Bengal, it was an inconsequential match as they were already out of the tournament. Yet they played their hearts out against Haryana and shot into the lead in the 23rd minute through Dular Marandi. Haryana, however, cancelled the lead a minute before halftime when redoubtable Rinu Rani found the equaliser.<br>In the second half, Bengal took the lead again, this time Player of the Match Mousumi Murmu put her team ahead in the 58th minute. But then, Haryana&#8217;s Tannu scored in the 80th minute to take the one crucial point for her side.<br>Earlier in the day, Railways took their tally of points to 12 with a narrow 1-0 win over Maharashtra. The losers fought well, but caved in five minutes before close when Yumnam Kamala Devi scored the all-important goal for the Railways. She was named the Player of the Match.<br>The other Group B match was of no consequence as both Manipur and Himachal Pradesh were already out of the tournament. Nevertheless, Manipur reduced the tie to a completely one-sided affair, winning the match 5-0.<br>Yumlembam Pakdi Devi, Irom Prameshwori Devi and Maibam Nandeshwori Devi scored a goal each, while Oinam Babita Devi struck twice and was later adjudged the Player of the Match.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/senior-women-football-cship-haryana-set-up-sf-match-with-odisha-indian-railways-to-meet-tamil-nadu/">Senior Women Football C&#8217;ship: Haryana set up SF match with Odisha, Indian Railways to meet Tamil Nadu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://box.online.mills.edu/senior-women-football-cship-haryana-set-up-sf-match-with-odisha-indian-railways-to-meet-tamil-nadu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saturday sport: Cork squeeze past Roscommon; Dublin trail Clare at half-time</title>
		<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/saturday-sport-cork-squeeze-past-roscommon-dublin-trail-clare-at-half-time/</link>
					<comments>https://box.online.mills.edu/saturday-sport-cork-squeeze-past-roscommon-dublin-trail-clare-at-half-time/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://box.online.mills.edu/?p=77</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Saturday sport: Cork squeeze past Roscommon; Dublin trail Clare at half-time Here&#8217;s the latest from the day&#8217;s sporting action&#8230; GAA The first of the All-Ireland Senior Football Championship preliminary quarter-finals have got underway. A late point for Cork at Páirc Ui Chaoimh has seen them past Roscommon on a scoreline of 1-14 to 0-16 to</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/saturday-sport-cork-squeeze-past-roscommon-dublin-trail-clare-at-half-time/">Saturday sport: Cork squeeze past Roscommon; Dublin trail Clare at half-time</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Saturday sport: Cork squeeze past Roscommon; Dublin trail Clare at half-time</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s the latest from the day&#8217;s sporting action&#8230;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">GAA</h3>



<p>The first of the All-Ireland Senior Football Championship preliminary quarter-finals have got underway.</p>



<p>A late point for Cork at Páirc Ui Chaoimh has seen them past Roscommon on a scoreline of 1-14 to 0-16 to take a place in the All-Ireland Football quarter-finals.</p>



<p>The second of the day&#8217;s preliminary quarter-finals between Kildare and Monaghan threw in at 4.45pm, while Ballybofey hosts Donegal v Tyrone from 7pm.</p>



<p>In the All-Ireland Hurling Championship, Dublin have built up a heavy deficit against Clare in the first of two quarter-finals at the Gaelic Grounds. The Banner lead 4-8 to 1-8 at half-time.</p>



<p>Later, Galway take on Tipperary from 6.15pm, with the winners of the two games meeting Limerick and Kilkenny in the semi-finals.</p>



<p>In Group Two of the All-Ireland Senior Camogie Championship, Kilkenny took a 4-13 to 1-4 win over Dublin at Parnell Park, while Tipperary lead Wexford 2-10 to 0-10 with just a few minutes gone in the second half in Bellefield.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Rugby</h3>



<p>Ireland have drawn 34-34 against England in their opening game at the under-20 World Rugby Championship in South Africa.</p>



<p>Next up for Ireland is Australia on Thursday at 10am Irish time.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Golf</h3>



<p>Leona Maguire leads the way heading into the third round at the Women&#8217;s PGA Championship in New Jersey.</p>



<p>Chasing a first major title, the Cavan woman is one shot clear of the field on five-under-par.</p>



<p>Stephanie Meadow is also well-placed on one-under.</p>



<p>Elsewhere, Rory McIlroy is seven shots off the lead ahead of his third round at the Travelers Championship.</p>



<p>He&#8217;s eight-under-par &#8211; with Denny McCarthy and Keegan Bradley at the head of the field on 15-under.</p>



<p>Shane Lowry is also through to the weekend on seven-under.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/saturday-sport-cork-squeeze-past-roscommon-dublin-trail-clare-at-half-time/">Saturday sport: Cork squeeze past Roscommon; Dublin trail Clare at half-time</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://box.online.mills.edu/saturday-sport-cork-squeeze-past-roscommon-dublin-trail-clare-at-half-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘If Divya Bharti was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work’: Tridev actor Sonam Khan remembers her only friend in the film industry</title>
		<link>https://box.online.mills.edu/if-divya-bharti-was-alive-today-a-lot-of-people-would-be-out-of-work-tridev-actor-sonam-khan-remembers-her-only-friend-in-the-film-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://box.online.mills.edu/if-divya-bharti-was-alive-today-a-lot-of-people-would-be-out-of-work-tridev-actor-sonam-khan-remembers-her-only-friend-in-the-film-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://box.online.mills.edu/?p=73</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>‘If Divya Bharti was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work’: Tridev actor Sonam Khan remembers her only friend in the film industry Yesteryear actor Sonam Khan, who is best known for her popular song from the film Tridev, has opened up about her friendship with the late actor&#160;Divya Bharti. Sonam</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/if-divya-bharti-was-alive-today-a-lot-of-people-would-be-out-of-work-tridev-actor-sonam-khan-remembers-her-only-friend-in-the-film-industry/">‘If Divya Bharti was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work’: Tridev actor Sonam Khan remembers her only friend in the film industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>‘If Divya Bharti was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work’: Tridev actor Sonam Khan remembers her only friend in the film industry</p>



<p>Yesteryear actor Sonam Khan, who is best known for her popular song from the film Tridev, has opened up about her friendship with the late actor&nbsp;<strong>Divya Bharti</strong>. Sonam said that Divya was a legend, and added that there was never any competition between them. The actor also recalled a hilarious anecdote about how they were once comparing their waist sizes.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In an interview with Siddharth Kannan, Sonam said, “It worked between us (her and Divya) because we were the same age, we laughed with each other and there was no competition between us. She even knew that I was going to quit acting. She was very nice. If she was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work.”</p>



<p>She added, “She was a very happy-go-lucky person and you get to see very few people like her. And the whole world knows that she was magic in front of the camera. Her looks were amazing and she was also a very bold girl, very ahead of her times. She would answer back to people on their face, be it any matter.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu/if-divya-bharti-was-alive-today-a-lot-of-people-would-be-out-of-work-tridev-actor-sonam-khan-remembers-her-only-friend-in-the-film-industry/">‘If Divya Bharti was alive today, a lot of people would be out of work’: Tridev actor Sonam Khan remembers her only friend in the film industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://box.online.mills.edu">BOX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://box.online.mills.edu/if-divya-bharti-was-alive-today-a-lot-of-people-would-be-out-of-work-tridev-actor-sonam-khan-remembers-her-only-friend-in-the-film-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
